learnseobasics.net 2013-05-23

# Privacy Policy | Learn Seo Basics

**1\. How We Protect Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**2\. Our Commitment To Childrens Privacy**  
We do not provide services or sell products to children. If you are below the age of 18, you may use our website only with the permission and active involvement of a parent or legal guardian. If you are a minor, please do not provide us or other website visitors with any personal information.

**3\. Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting IMLeaks.net, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**4\. Links to third party Websites**  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

**5\. Refund Policy**  
If you find after purchase, any of our own product is not completing your requirements. Contact us to get the full refund on your demand in 15days after the date of purchase.

**6\. Policy Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will send an email notifying you of any changes.  
If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of LearnSeoBasics.net then you may contact us.
